Hello to my Korean
readers,
and maybe even my publisher.
I'm sitting here in Maui, Hawaii
taking a bit of a break from my tour and I just received word that
sales of 12 rules for life in Korea are approaching the hundred thousand mark, so I'm extremely gratified to hear that
I'm a great admirer of South Korean culture. I think that what you
your people have managed in the last 40 years is nothing short of a miracle and
Filled with admiration for your accomplishments
I would really hope that twelve rules for life can help you people
young and old alike
and encourage them to develop a compelling vision for their life and to take on this sort of
responsibility that you've been masters at managing
And to speak honestly and forthrightly and to live nobly and to bury your suffering properly and to help make the world
better and less malevolent place
and so
thank you for all your support so far and I hope at some point to be able to come to your country and perhaps
Talk to you
Thanks very much
Dr. Jordan Peterson.
Bye bye.